Kiss your class goodbye!
School Spirit is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Mike Gan.
A group of social outcasts, stuck in weekend detention, find themselves stalked by
their school’s urban legend who is set on killing bad students.
Erica Yang, played by Annie Q. Riegel.
Brett Callaway, played by Corey Fogelmanis.
Lizzy Whitmore, played by Jessi Case.
Vic Castro, played by Julian Works.
Russ Jones, played by Philip Labes.
Mr. Armstrong, played by Hugo Armstrong.
Teen Spirit is a 2018 musical drama film written and directed
by Max Minghella (in his directorial debut).
The film stars Elle Fanning, Rebecca Hall, and Zlatko Burić.
The film had its world premiere at the Toronto
International Film Festival on September 7, 2018.
It was released in the United States on April 12, 2019, by LD Entertainment and
Bleecker Street, and in the United Kingdom on July 26, 2019, by Lionsgate.
The film explores themes of holiday, murder,
urban legend, serial killer, school.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.